Did we see Pink Lady Apples wants to
know. Did you see or did you enjoy Bad
Bunny on Sunday?
Bad Bunny, I watched it after the fact.
Oh, I watched it. And
you know,
John, we haven't had this we haven't
talked about this.
I understand some of the right-wing
pushback, not all of it because look, he
is American. I mean, Puerto Rico is
American.
But
I will say my only my critique really
was there should have been subtitles.
Absolutely true. I don't speak a lick of
Spanish. I I will say
and don't mock me, but until 2 weeks
ago, I never heard of Bad Bunny.
Never heard of the man. Mhm. Um
tell you the truth, when I first heard
of him, I thought he I just assumed he
was a black rapper.
Yeah, me too. I didn't know anything
about it. So anyway, I watched it live
cuz I thought, well, people are going to
be talking about it cuz it's already
controversial, so I should watch it just
so I know what the heck I'm talking
about. Didn't understand a single word.
I did enjoy the creativity. I did. Mhm.
And then the next day
when
the Washington Post, the New York Times
translated the lyrics, Mhm. I was like,
"Oh, I get it." Yeah. So now I can say,
"Yes, I enjoyed it."
Now that I understand it.
>> You when you And the thing is I I've had
this argument with several people about
the you know, the subtitles. And I'm
like, "Look, when you go to the opera,
which is usually in Italian, they give
you a translation." That's right, they
do. And and I mean, because you miss out
a lot. Yes. So, you know, I mean, to me
it's exactly the same thing. Um to me,
Puerto Rico is as American as apple pie.
That's not the issue. Um it's like you
know, like if there was a zydeco you
know, performance,
that doesn't exist in France, right?
That's only American. Um that should
have a translation. Yeah. You know, just
because it's
I mean, you
>> we're in America. Um, exactly. Folk
style scrub, maybe I'm I'm unschooled,
but it seemed disrespectful to have a
Puerto Rican independence flag at an
American event. And for people who are
unaware of what that reference is to,
uh, Bad Bunny was carrying a Puerto
Rican flag around. If you look
carefully, the the blue field is lighter
than the, uh, than the normal Puerto
Rican flag that doesn't dark blue. And
that's the, uh, independence. Now, I
will say I do I did feel like
I that that was a contra- a
contradiction, right? It's an internal
conflict between the message that like,
you know, uh,
Spanish and Puerto Rican and Latino
culture are part of the United States,
all to be celebrated, and at the same
time we want to be independent. Those
two things politically don't go
together, John. No, you're you're you're
right. Yeah, I think you and I've talked
about this the
the last time I went to Puerto Rico,
um,
I was talking with a, um,
with a guy, he's kind of mid-level
Puerto Rican government official. And I
asked him to explain to me what people's
positions were on, um,
on independence. And he said, "Oh, we
are
very evenly divided." He said, "Fully a
third of Puerto Ricans want
independence. A third of Puerto Ricans
want statehood. Uh, to be to be a member
of the United States as a state. And a
third of Puerto Ricans want to just
leave things exactly the way they are
right now."
And he said, "And because of that,
nothing's ever going to change."
Yeah, that's my understanding as well
when I went to Puerto Rico. Um, I mean,
yeah, uh, personally, if I were Puerto
Rican, I think I'd want independence,
but, you know,
>> I I would agree. Uh, I mean, I never
understood why the Scots voted not to be
independent from from the Brits.
>> I was shocked by that outcome. I was
stunned.
I really believed that was going to be
it. It was going to be
I thought it wasn't even going to be
close. Uh
agreed.
Yes.
>> not like the Scots couldn't handle
themselves economically. They have a
viable economy. They could Yeah.
I don't know. Yes. Uh John, what are
your thoughts about Ghislaine Maxwell
potentially getting a pardon from Trump
based on her silence and testimony to
try to absolve him? Well, she didn't
testify. She went She She She took the
fifth on everything. Why do you think
she I mean, my take on that is I thought
I assumed she didn't take the fifth
because basically they didn't offer her
anything and therefore why should she
say anything? At the very least they
would normally have offered limited
immunity. At the most they would have
let her just speak her peace and and she
couldn't be prosecuted for anything.
That's how Oliver North ended up never
going to prison. Because he was offered
immunity, he testified, the Justice
Department then tried to charge him, and
the Supreme Court said, "You can't
charge him because Congress gave him
immunity, so nothing he said can be used
against him." He ended up not seeing a
day in jail.
Um with Ghislaine Maxwell,
I think they just didn't offer her
anything. They just subpoenaed her at
the prison said, "Come and testify." And
she said, "Not a chance."
Right.
I don't know what
what they thought would happen.
>> And the more the more important point is
this notion of a pardon or a
commutation.
Um like deep down I can't imagine any
president
commuting the sentence of or pardoning a
convicted child trafficker. Especially
at that scale. But I'm I'm genuinely
worried.
Uh Katie Catastrophe is asking, "Elon
said he would pay the legal fees of any
Epstein survivor if they get sued for
speaking out." Although Elon's promises
online prove not to always to be uh you
know, bankable. Think he's just trying
to get ahead of it showing he's a
changed man.
I think it's just Elon trolling. Yeah.
Um
Question from Jessica Davidson. Lately
the media is starting to promote promote
the idea that Epstein was working for
Israel all along. Who was it who
suggested that several months back,
John?
>> Exactly right.
True. Exactly right. I'm very proud to
say and
Alan Dershowitz and I went to the mat
over this
on the Piers Morgan show. I'm proud to
say I stood up to him.
Um but uh yeah, I maintain from the very
beginning this had all the hallmarks of
a of a uh
an Israeli access agent operation. I
stand by that and I believe I've been
proven correct. It it it appears so.
Okay, uh question for John from Desert
Fox. What's your opinion on recent
settler agitation about Al-Aqsa in
coordination with the looming Iran war?
Many extremists see this as a biblical
end-time battle of Gog and Magog. That
is exactly right. I am
I am actually frightened by all of this.
You know, the
religious Jews believe that
that they need to reclaim
uh
the the mount, right? And build the
third temple. The first temple, of
course, was BC. The second temple was
destroyed, I don't know, 30 years or so
after the crucifixion.
And
this is where the third temple will
come. As soon as the third temple is
built, the Messiah is going to come down
and take everybody to heaven.
It's it's apocalyptic. It's exceedingly
dangerous.
And honest to God, if something happens
to the Al-Aqsa mosque, it's going to be
the start of World War III.
Uh well, that's good.
>> It is. It's going to be the start of
World War III. Um Alex, John, did uh did
you vaccinate before going overseas
deployments? From what I heard, the
rules are very strict. Yeah, all of us
Oh my god, you know
when I first joined the CIA all the way
up until like 2000. So, for that whole
decade for yellow fever, you had to get
a gamma globulin shot. And it was like
injecting maple syrup in your butt, and
it would make this knot the size of a
tennis ball. So, they would give you
dispensation to walk around the compound
for an hour and stretch out your glutes
so you didn't get that giant ball. It
was like an hour of administrative time
to work out that ball of gamma globulin
that's pooling in your butt. But, yeah,
we got
Uh, and another thing too is you'd get
all these shots the same day, and the
next day you're sick as a dog.
And so, we would get that day off
without it counting
against your sick leave. Um, but yeah,
and I only went to not only, but I
almost exclusively went to um,
the countries as Donald Trump
called them. And so, uh, so I was
getting shots right right, left, and
center every time I'd go. God, that
sounds horrible. I only
>> add Let me add one thing if I could.
>> [clears throat]
>> I caught typhoid fever in Bangkok in
2002.
And
it's the sickest I've ever been in my
life. And when it was finally diagnosed
as typhoid fever, I said, "But I said it
can't be typhoid fever because I got the
I got the shots. I got the typhoid
shots."
>> Yeah.
And the doctor said,
"The typhoid shots don't prevent you
from getting typhoid fever. The typhoid
shots make the typhoid fever slightly
less virulent when you catch it."
Gotcha. That It was like the worst case
of the flu I've ever had in my my I had
to go to the hospital twice.
Wow. It was bad.
I have not I I only have I I remember
when you that you you I had a flashback
to those big needles. Um I had the first
time I went to Central Asia, I had to
get hepatitis shot your ass like sort of
like in It was It felt like the needle
was still in there like a month
afterwards. Yes.
And the needle's huge and it's thick.
Yeah, it's bad. It's bad.
>> [music]